https://stannesflorist.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
111 Newcastle Street Perth WA 6000   (08) 9388 8844
COVID-19 Update - We are OPEN & completing contactless Flower & Hamper Deliveries around Perth!
Log In
My Cart:
0 item(s)
Search:
Search
St Anne's Florist & Gift Baskets Perth
Categories
FLOWERS ARRANGEMENTSBOUQUETSROSESROSES IN A HAT BOXFLOWERS IN A BOXCORSAGESBUTTONHOLES & BOUTONNIERESANZAC & REMEMBRANCE DAY WREATHSHAMPERSSTAY AT HOME ISOLATION HAMPERS & GIFTSFOOD & WINE HAMPERS FRUIT HAMPERS PAMPER HAMPERS & GIFTSGET WELL HAMPERSBABY & KIDS GIFTSBABY HAMPERS BABY FLOWERS NEWBORN BABY GIFTS KIDS HAMPERS & GIFTSSYMPATHYSYMPATHY FOR HOME FUNERAL WREATHS FUNERAL CASKET SPRAYSBALLOONSHELIUM BALLOONS LATEX BALLOONS BALLOON BOUQUETS 9 INCH STICK BALLOONSWALKING BALLOONS MEGALOON BALLOONSGIANT BALLOONSSOFT TOYSTEDDY BEARSSOFT TOYS DOLLS WHEAT BAGSPLANT GIFTSGIFT ADD ONSALCOHOL GIFTSCHAMPAGNECHOCOLATES CHOCOLATE BOUQUETS BEERCANDLES GIFTS
FLOWERS
ARRANGEMENTS
BOUQUETS
ROSES
ROSES IN A HAT BOX
FLOWERS IN A BOX
CORSAGES
BUTTONHOLES & BOUTONNIERES
Privacy Policy
This policy sets out how Woodsome Pty Ltd (trading as St Anne’s Florist and Gift Baskets) (“St Anne’s”) collects, uses and discloses your personal information.
By accessing or using St Anne’s services you agree to the use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this policy.
St Anne's and Privacy
St Anne’s is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
What personal information is collected
St Anne’s collects personal information that it considers necessary for it to provide the range of services it offers.
Personal information collected by St Anne’s may include:
Your name, address and contact details
The name, address and contact details of the intended recipient
Your credit account details
The services provided to you and the intended recipient
Records and content of communications with St Anne’s
The content of personalised card messages between yourself and the intended recipient
How is personal information used?
Your personal information may be used for the following purposes:
To provide the services requested by you
To manage those services including customer service and billing
To promote and market special offers and other services to you. If you do not want to receive these, please contact St Anne’s at the address provided below.
How is personal information disclosed?
St Anne’s may disclose personal information to individuals or organisations other than St Anne’s. The organisations to which we may disclose personal information include:
Interflora – St Anne’s will share personal information with Interflora for the limited purpose of fulfilling customer orders
Government and regulatory authorities – St Anne’s will share personal information as required by law or in cases where unlawful activities, such as fraudulent credit card use is suspected
How can you access your personal information?
You generally have a right to access your personal information. If you wish to access your personal information, please contact St Anne’s at the address provided below. Please remember to provide as much detail as you can as this will help us find the information. There may or may not be a charge for this service. If there is a charge, it will not be excessive.
What if you do not provide personal information?
If you choose not to provide personal information when requested, St Anne’s may not be able to provide you with the full range of services it offers.
St Anne’s website and personal information
When you visit the St Anne’s website, the website records anonymous information such as IP address, time, date, referring url, pages accessed, type of browser and operating system.
Cookies
St Anne’s Florist website uses cookies. A cookie is a small file that stays on your computer until you turn off your computer or it expires (typically between 30 and 90 days), depending on whether it is a sessional or persistent cookie.
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's technical information. In general, we use the information that is collected through the use of cookies on our Site to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor your experience with us and our communications with you to meet your special interests and needs.
The use of cookies is an industry standard and most major websites use them. Most internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your internet browser to disable cookies or to warn when cookies are being used. If cookies are disable St Anne’s may not be able to provide you with the full range of services that it offers.
Cookies may collect and store your personal information. This policy applies to personal information collected by cookies.
Cookies are used by St Anne’s to track selection of products in your shopping cart and to help detect unlawful activity, such as fraudulent credit card use.
Security and personal information
St Anne’s takes reasonable steps to protect personal information collected from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modifications and disclosure.
St Anne’s online shopping cart uses a Secure Form (SSL) to collect credit card information. The credit card form securely encrypts your credit account details. However, if you prefer not to send your credit account details to St Anne’s over the internet, you can send them via fax or provide them over telephone on the numbers listed below.
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
St Anne's contact details
If you have a problem, complaint, want to change your personal information or just wish to enquire about privacy, please contact us.
St Anne's Florist and Gift Baskets 111 Newcastle Street, PERTH WA 6000 Tel: 08 9388 8844 Fax: 08 9228 3126 Email: info@stannesflorist.com.au
How this policy changes
This policy may change over time. All changes will be published on this website.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Go!
Call us now:
(08) 9388-8844 111 Newcastle Street Perth WA 6000
© 2020 Anne's Florist & Gift Baskets Perth. All Rights Reserved.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
